Finding aid for the Connexxus/Centro de Mujeres collection, 1985-1991 LSC.1848
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Publicity and Publications, 1984-1990; Series 7.; 2 boxes, 1.5 linear feet
  - Newsletters, 1985-1990; Subseries 1.; 48 folders
    The Newsletters subseries contains a full run of Connexxus newsletters which were published monthly. It also contains incomplete runs of the Connexxus Business and and Professional Women's Alliance (CBPWA) newsletter and the Volunteer Connexxion newsletter.
    - Connexxus Newsletters, 1985-1990 (Box 10, Folder 1 - 46)
      Folder 1: February - August 1985
      Folder 2: October - December 1985
      Folder 3: January 1986
      Folder 4: March 1986
      Folder 5: January 1987
      Folder 6: February 1987
      Folder 7: March 1987
      Folder 8: April 1987
      Folder 9: May 1987
      Folder 10: June 1987
      Folder 11: July 1987
      Folder 12: August 1987
      Folder 13: September 1987
      Folder 14: October 1987
      Folder 15: November 1987
      Folder 16: December 1987
      Folder 17: January 1988
      Folder 18: February 1988, inserts only*
      Folder 10: March 1988
      Folder 11: April 1988
      Folder 12: May 1988
      Folder 13: June 1988
      Folder 14: July 1988
      Folder 15: August 1988
      Folder 16: September 1988
      Folder 17: October 1988
      Folder 18: November 1988
      Folder 19: December 1988
      Folder 29: January 1989
      Folder 30: February 1989
      Folder 31: March 1989
      Folder 32: April 1989
      Folder 33: May 1989
      Folder 34: June 1989
      Folder 35: July 1989
      Folder 36: August 1989
      Folder 37: September 1989
      Folder 39: October 1989
      Folder 40: November 1989
      Folder 41: December 1989
      Folder 41: January 1990
      Folder 42: February 1990
      Folder 43: March 1990
      Folder 44: April 1990
      Folder 45: May 1990
      Folder 46: June 1990
      * Folder 18 only contains the inserts from the February 1988 newsletter. See the Publicity Volumes in Box 11 for a copy of the February 1988 (Volume 4, Number 2) issue.
    - Connexxus Business and Professional Women's Alliance (CBPWA) / The Alliance Newsletters, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 47)
      1986: January, March-April, September-October, December
      1987: January-February, April-December
      1988: January-April
    - The Volunteer Connexxion: The Newsletter for Connexxus Volunteers, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 48)
      1986: April, May-June, September-December
      1987: January-May, July